

CONTACT ME AT

- Valencia, Carabobo
 Venezuela
- lugoa9292@gmail.com
- https://lugoa92.github.io/site/
- Whatsapp +58 424 494 64 21
- ▼ Telegram +58 424 494 64 21
- in <u>@lugoa92</u>

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Second Language)
- French (Advanced)
- Portuguese (Basic)
- Japanese (Basic)

ARTURO ALEJANDRO LUGO SANTAMARIA

SALES MANAGER MARKETING SPECIALIST UX TRANSLATOR CONTENT WRITER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Efficient and effective sales representative with over 5 years of experience in a variety of products sales, marketing and merchandising. Exceed in allocating resources and identifying business oportunities. Interested in seeking a position that welcomes initiative.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales Representative

Dist. Pindar 11.11 December 2019 - Current Venezuela

- Developed, evaluated and continually review marketing programs for assigned products to ensure the programs meet the established objectives.
- Investigated the competition, developed and continually evaluate the pricing structure of assigned product line to ensure the Company maintains a profit margin on the product line and the Company remains competitive with the marketplace.
- Represent the Company at various trade shows, ensuring that our products are displayed appropriately and that the right communication material is available for distribution as well negotiates with outside vendor and internal departments as appropriate.
- Provide ideas for the organization's Web Site structure and ensure the new information is regularly added to the site and all other communications media.

Writer and Translator

Sportechnutricion December 2015 - Current Freelancer

- Composer of articles, short stories, translations from English to Spanish and vice-versa.
- Translation from French to English or Spanish



SKILLS SUMMARY

- Proofreading, translating, researching skills and decision-making ability
- Capability to work under pressure in a fast changing environment
- Detail oriented
- Ability to work both independently and as a part of a team
- Problem Solving
- Customer Service
- Communication
- Resourceful, adaptable and easily able to acquire and apply new skills immediately.
- Negotiation
- Marketing
- U)

CERTIFICATIONS RECEIVED

- English Course for Beginners (2020)
- English Workshop for Beginners (2020)
- Basic English Course: Fundamentals (2020)
- Basic English Course: Grammar (2020)
- Basic English Course: Pronunciation (2020)
- Basic English Course: Conversation (2020)
- Intermediate English Course: Grammar (2020).

ARTURO ALEJANDRO LUGO SANTAMARIA

SALES MANAGER MARKETING SPECIALIST UX TRANSLATOR CONTENT WRITER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Manager

Dist. Ensof, C.A.

December 2015 - December 2017

Venezuela

- Delegating responsibilities and supervising business operations.
- Monitoring storage activity and ensuring it is properly provisioned and staffed.
- Analyzing information and processes and developing more effective or efficient processes and strategies.
- Establishing and achieving business and profit objectives, generating reports and presenting information to upper-level managers or other parties.
- Other duties to ensure the overall health and success of the business.

Sales Representative

Dist. Ensof, C.A.

December 2010 - December 2015

Venezuela

- Identifying leads, educating prospects on products, trainings, presentations, and providing existing customers with exceptional support.
- Acomplishing sales through meetings, phone calls or even whatsapp chats.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Bachelor of Modern Languages Business Mention

Arturo Michelena University F.H.L.A. School of Letters 2014 - 2020

• Studied project planning, coordination, and ethics

Bachelor of Science

U.E Colegio Juan Manuel Cajigal 2003-2010